DOR RAFALIN

COMMERCIAL LAWYER

Date of birth: October 12th, 1987

Nationality: German (being also an Israeli national)

3, Rue des Arbustes, L-5951, Itzig, Luxembourg

Tel: +352621759140 **Email:** dor.raf@gmail.com



Experienced lawyer and mediator with proven background, deep understanding and interest in cross-border legal proceedings. Skilled in drafting contracts and documents of incorporation. Skilled in five languages.

EDUCATION

Bar Ilan University, Faculty of Law

Ramat Gan, Israel

2016-2017 - Master of Law (LL.M.) (cum laude).

Among top students (dean's list).

<u>Course focus</u>: Alternative Dispute Resolution at local and international level (**certification in mediation**).

IDC, Faculties of Law and Governance

Tel-Aviv. Israel

2011-2015 - Bachelor of Law (LL.B.).

Course focus: Corporate and Commercial Law and International Conflict Resolution.

WORK EXPERIENCE

GESTMAN S.A.

Luxembourg Ville, Luxembourg

August 2019- Legal Assistant.

Assistance in internal procedures related to KYC And AML, relationship with banks, changing leal and regualtury framework of clients and collecting debts.

Bonn Steichen & Partners (BSP)

Luxembourg Ville, Luxembourg

April 2019- July 2019- Legal Intern.

Legal assistance in respect of Capital Markets Laws for public companies operating at the Luxembourg Stock Exchange, carrying out KYC and AML researches, assisting in the preparation of legal deeds and opinions and writing legal notes in the Banking Department.

Permanent Delegation of Israel to the OECD

Paris, France

2018-2019 - Advisor for Legal Affairs; Transportation; Environment; Security and Privacy in the Digital Economy.

Prepared a draft report on the compliance of Israeli Corporate Law with the objectives of the Paris Agreement on Climate Change.

Mariola Hawel-Tocker and Co. Law Firm

Bnei Brak, Israel

2017-2018 - Commercial attorney.

Drafted real estate sales contracts.

Drafted documents of incorporation for Israeli companies in Israel and Poland.

Handled requests to administrative and judicial authorities in Israel and Poland in commercial and real estate matters.

Bar Ilan University, Faculty of Law

Ramat-Gan, Israel

2016-2017 - Research and teaching assistant in Public and Private International Law.

Assisted in writing articles dealing with Conflict of Laws in Contract and Corporate Laws.

International Department at the State

Jerusalem, Israel

Attorney's Office

2015-2016 - Legal Intern.

Handled requests for Extraditions, Mutual Legal Assistance, Transfer of Prisoners, Child Abduction; legal research.

Dan Assan Law Office

Tel Aviv, Israel

2014-2015 - Legal Intern.

Translated documents and did legal research related to German and Austrian commercial and civil Laws.

Criminal Department at the Tel-Aviv

Tel Aviv, Israel

District Attorney's office 2012-2013 - Legal Intern.

Drafted legal documents and did legal research.

LANGUAGES

English and Hebrew: full proficiency; German: very good working knowledge;

Polish and Italian: good command; French, Maltese and Slovenian: basic.

INTERESTS

Traveling, reading, painting and photography.